surveycompare.co.in 2017-12-06

# MVF Global Ltd

Survey Compare ("We", "our" and/or "us") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We treat with the utmost care the personal information you may supply to us on my.surveycompare.net.

This policy (together with our [terms of use](http://www2.mvfglobal.com/surveycompare_terms_of_use/2fe42/85d50) and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **Act** ), the data controller is MVF Global Ltd which is a trading name of ours with our registered address being Ryland House, 23a Ryland Road, London, NW5 3EH. We are a company registered in England and Wales under company number 06951544. Marketing VF Ltd is registered under the Act, ref PZ1995728.

### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site my.surveycompare.net ( **our site** ). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access. 

#### IP ADDRESSES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

#### COOKIES

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our [Cookie Policy](http://www2.mvfglobal.com/cookie_policy_en/52fa2/1cff4)

We use interest-based advertising tools provided by Google - these include but are not limited to 'remarketing', 'interest categories', 'similar audiences' and other types of interest-based advertising. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with the Marketing VF Limited website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by Marketing VF Limited to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show Marketing VF Limited ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Marketing VF Limited’s website.

To opt out of customized Google Display Network ads click [here](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&hl=en&hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjTHv3OaB4S8hINeTAfjctkUvYN2B5sDrcqQ_TIU8L0MBqxnQAr20ZYP5ZPJ54Wg0fWXoy5GAKagHxjOCGFZw1-wLorykJbqxcUH9tiJxZ_MmI6jmlMaORAJPGAbHwVsXGJsWbA9BZxTrj4WrFycSFajwgmgoKK5c52sOewGhjd6E1kbnrkXuoDT0lT-7DONrlIaipv). To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

Any information collected is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose.

#### WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed outside the EEA by us or by one of our suppliers for the purposes of, but not limited to, sorting and collating information before it is passed to our clients. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

#### USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To pass on to both specific companies mentioned and also to others we think may be appropriate based on and in accordance with the information and permission you provide to us.
  * To facilitate communication between yourself and our clients.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also provide our clients with aggregated information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help our clients reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our clients’ wishes by displaying their goods or services to that target audience.

#### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Marketing VF Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms of use](http://www2.mvfglobal.com/surveycompare_terms_of_use/2fe42/85d50) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Marketing VF Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes other than for those purposes listed above. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for any such additional purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any additional third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at $unsubscribe$.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

#### CONTACT

MVF GLOBAL Ltd  
Ryland House  
24a Ryland Road  
London  
NW5 3EH

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@surveycompare.net.
